theshoreclubtc.com 2018-06-29

# Privacy Statement | The Shore Club on Long Bay

Your Privacy Matters

The Shore Club on Long Bay (“The Shore Club”) is aware of the need to address Internet privacy issues, and you should be aware of how or our organization treats any information about you that we may receive via the Internet as a result of your visit to this site.

You may visit our website without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Our web servers may automatically collect domain names, IP addresses and anonymous referring links of our visitors, but they do not collect email addresses or any other personal information without consent. The website collects Google demographics and interest data so we can better understand how to deliver services. You may select to opt-out of this feature by installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Add-on. Here is the link to this Add-on: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/

Use of Any Personal Information Provided

The Shore Club collects personal information from this web site – through its online forms, e-mail list registrations, etc. – ONLY for the purposes of continuing future correspondence. All personal information collected is held in the strictest confidence. Any personal information obtained, in addition to any personal information that you voluntarily provided us, such as contact details, demographics, intended product application, and experience with our products and/or services, may be used only for the following purposes:

  * To provide information on our products and/or services to you;
  * To administer and maintain our records;
  * To perform internal customer service monitoring;
  * To ensure that the service we offer you continues to be the most appropriate service for your needs;
  * To respond to any query that you may raise with us;
  * To provide an enhanced service to you;
  * To perform research and statistical analysis.

The Shore Club does not use your personal information for any other purpose other than that stated above, nor does it sell, rent or otherwise improperly disclose this information to outside parties.

The Shore Club may disclose information to other companies within the same group of companies as The Shore Club.

The period of use of the personal data supplied by you will not be longer than deemed necessary by The Shore Club or any of its group of companies.

For more information, please contact reservations@theshoreclubtc.com.
